centralreach.com 2016-04-30

# CentralReach | Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how CentralReach collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Website.

CentralReach has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that our privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through this Website, www.crwebsitenew.wpengine.com, and does not cover data that may have been collected behind the login on our site. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@centralreach.com](mailto:info@centralreach.com).

**What information do you collect?**  
We collect the following personal information from you: Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number. As is true of most Websites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages and operating system.

When using the CentralReach website, you will never provide CentralReach with Protected Health Information (PHI) nor will CentralReach provide you.

**What is the information used for?**  
_This collected information is used to:_  
• Personalize your experience on the Website  
• Send you requested product or service information  
• Send product updates via email  
• Improve customer service  
• Administer your account  
• Respond to your questions and concerns  
• Administer contest, promotion, survey or other site features

We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified above and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

**Do you disclose my information?**  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, if CentralReach is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**How long do you keep my information?**  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**How can I opt in/out of emails?**  
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at 1-800-939-5414.

**How can I access my account?**  
Please note that users can not update or delete previously submitted information. If your information (such as your email address) should change, we ask that you re-submit a registration form or request.

**Do you use web cookies, beacons, and widgets?**  
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. Third Party Cookies: The use of cookies by our partners is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web Beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

Our Website includes Widgets and social media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, Twitter follow button, and Google+ button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. These are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Do you post customer testimonials?**  
We post customer testimonials, comments, and reviews on our Website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from Testimonials or comments please contact us.

**Do you link to other websites?**  
Our Site includes links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of CentralReach. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Website you visit.

**How do you secure my information?**  
CentralReach has numerous security measures in place to help protect sensitive data within the system. These measures include a sign-in protected by SSL security. Your browser will usually display an indicator (such as a “lock” icon) when using a secure SSL connection. All CentralReach software applications communicate with a server hosted entirely by CentralReach. All communications are secured with public-key encryption.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. To report a security violation, please promptly call us at 1-800-939-5414.

**Changes**  
CentralReach may revise and update the Privacy Policy at any time, without notice to you. We encourage you to periodically reread this policy, to see if there have been any changes to our policies that may affect you. This policy was last modified August 12, 2015.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding on our privacy policy, please write to us at:

CentralReach, LLC  
Attention: Privacy and Security  
PO Box 5430  
Lighthouse Point, FL 33074
